CONTACT



Kosia861@gmail.com



Enugu, Nigeria

TOOLS

Figma, Adobe XD, Invision

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

User Research, User Interface Design, User Experience Design, Technical writing, Web design.

SOCIAL



twitter.com/lucy_asogwa



linkedin.com/in/lucy-asogwa



dribble.com/Lu-cee



www.behance.net/lucyasogwa

Portfolio Link:

https://lucyasogwa.herokuapp.com

Lucy Asogwa

UI/UX DESIGNER

SUMMARY

Lucy is a dedicated and passionate Ui/Ux designer who creates user friendly interfaces that enables users understand how to use complex and technical products by conducting user research, conducting usability testing, developing wireframes and task flows based on user's needs and collaborating with developers to create intuitive, user-friendly softwares and to deliver an outstanding user experience providing an exceptional and intuitive application design.

SKILLS

User Research, User Interface Design, User Experience Design, Wireframing, prototyping.

EXPERIENCE

- Freelancer at upwork
- Shecodeafrica, Remote-Internship December 2020-March 2021
- Zuritraining, Remote-Internship March 2021-June 2021
- Nipost Company
 August 2021-September 2021

FREELANCE UI/UX DESIGNER

- * Collaborating with software developer and design teams in creating solutions for users problems
- * Conducting user research on potential products and features
- * Designing user interfaces and experiences to meet user's needs
- * Colloaborating with teams in conducting user researchs and creating case studies

PERSONAL PROJECT

Aiwe app

Conducted user research with surveys, questionnaires and interviews

Created a case study consisting of the overview, the challange, journey maps, user flows, personas and the solution

Created low, mid and high fidelity wireframes and prototypes

EDUCATION HISTORY

Udemy - Ui/Ux design course-January 2021-Febuary 2021

Enugu State University of Science and Techonology, Undergraduate, LLB-2020-PRESENT

Learning Figma user interfaces design essentials- October 2021- December 2021

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Positive Attitude, Good Communication Skills, Good Time Management, Quick Learning Ability, Good Team Player, Big-Picture Focus HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT